(Sheldon:)You know, in the future,
when we're disembodied brains in jars...
(Sheldon:)...we're going to look back on this
as eight hours well wasted.
I don't wanna be in a jar.
I want my brain in an android body.
(Raj:)Eight feet tall and ripped.
(Howard:)I'm with you. I just have to make sure
if I'm a synthetic human, I'd still be Jewish.
(Howard:)I promised my mother.
(Raj:)I suppose you could have
your android penis circumcised.
(Raj:)That's something your rabbi would have
to discuss with the manufacturer.
(Sheldon:)Not to mention
you'd have to power down on Saturdays.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, why is this letter in the trash?
(Sheldon:)Well, there's always the possibility...
(Sheldon:)...that a trash can spontaneously
formed around the letter...
...but Ockham's Razor would suggest
that someone threw it out.
(Leonard:)It's from the Institute
for Experimental Physics.
(Leonard:)They want us to present our
paper on the properties of supersolids...